(Joy:)My pee is gonna
stink up the place.
(Howard:)I think she likes you.
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)EZ Aquarii B...
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)EZ Aquarii C...
(Sheldon(wearing a heavy coat and false nose and glasses):)Excuse me, madam.
(Amy:)Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Rats!
(Amy:)I believe a misunderstanding
may have occurred
(Amy:)when I asked you
to meet my mother.
(Sheldon:)No misunderstanding.
(Sheldon:)I've learned what that
request actually means,
(Sheldon:)and I don't want to be
joined to another object
(Leonard:)by an inclined plane wrapped
helically around an axis.
(Amy:)In what way are
you screwed?
(Amy:)All I want to do is present you
as my boyfriend to my mother
(Amy:)so she'll be satisfied
that I'm in a relationship.
(Sheldon:)So we'd be
perpetrating a ruse?
(Amy:)Precisely.